Hyunggi Chang

https://www.cv-learn.com

Github: changh95 | SlideShare: HyunggiChang Email: hyunggi.chang95@gmail.com Mobile: (+82) 010-2885-4493

SUMMARY

I am interested in 3D computer vision and SLAM algorithms for mobile devices (VR/AR/Robotics). I have experiences on developing robust and safe perception algorithms for spatial AI system. To build an efficient and safe spatial AI system, I follow state-of-the-art algorithms and practise test-driven development.

EMPLOYMENT

• StradVision Algorithm Engineer - Semantic SLAM (Full-time) Seoul. South Korea

Jun. 2021 - Present

- o Implement visual SLAM algorithms, using deep semantic features and road environment information.
- Verify performance and safety via auto-benchmark using continuous integration and development (CI/CD).
- Design modular software architecture, which complies with ASPICE and ISO 26262.

• Virnect Seoul. South Korea

Computer Vision Research Engineer / Manager (Full-time)

Apr. 2019 - May 2021

- Developed pose estimation and visual localization algorithms for mobile apps in the Perception & ML team.
- Developed visual tracking software for a number of research projects in the Research Centre.
- Designed and built an automatic test & benchmark system for continuous integration and development (CI/CD).

• McKinsey & Company

London, UK

Market Research (Part-time)

Oct. 2017 - Dec. 2017

• Performed market research in the AI & Robotics market as the lead student researcher.

Projects

• Vision-based auto valet parking system (Ongoing)

Semantic mapping of parking lot and vehicle localization.

- Simultaneous localization and mapping (SLAM) using multiple fisheye cameras.
- o Sensor fusion of semantic visual features (e.g. road markers) and wheel odometry.

• Mobile Augmented Reality SDK - Track SDK [LINK]

Cross-platform SDK for developing Augmented Reality (AR) applications.

- Developed pose estimation and visual tracking algorithms, such as Image/QR/Model-based tracking and SLAM.
- Easily Reconfigurable Marker-Based Tool Tracking Module

Software module that enables easy object pose estimation on pen-shaped objects by using AR markers.

- Hyperspectral Wide-field Endoscopic Image Registration and Structure-from-Motion 3D reconstruction of cancer that are invisible by eye, using multi-fibre hyperspectral endoscope.
- Mobile Rover for Environment Mapping and Survivor Detection in Disaster Scenarios

Voice-controllable rover, using RGB-D SLAM, object detection, and collision-avoidance - 1st Prize winner in Hackathon.

SKILLS

- Programming C17, C++17 (SSE/Neon), Python, Swift, Rust, MATLAB
- Vision/SLAM OpenCV, Eigen, TensorFlow, PyTorch, Ceres-solver
- Collaboration Git/GitHub, Docker, Linux, JIRA, TDD, Agile

EDUCATION

• Imperial College London M.Res. Medical Robotics and Image-Guided Intervention (Merit) • Course representative, Journal club lead	London, UK Oct. 2017 – Sept. 2018
 University of Warwick B.Eng. Manufacturing and Mechanical Engineering (Upper-Second Class Hons.) Course representative, University ambassador 	Coventry, UK Oct. 2014 – Jun. 2017
RESEARCH EXPERIENCES	
• Cavendish Laboratory, University of Cambridge Visiting Researcher (Advisor: Dr. Sarah Bohndiek)	Cambridgeshire, UK Jan. 2019 - Mar. 2019
• Surgical Imaging and Biophotonics Laboratory, Imperial College London M.Res Student Researcher (Advisor: Prof. Daniel Elson)	London, UK Jan. 2018 - Sept. 2018
• HARMS Lab, Imperial College London M.Res Student Researcher (Advisor: Dr. George Mynolas)	London, UK Oct. 2017 - Dec. 2017
• Trace Metals in Medicine Laboratory, University of Warwick B.Eng Student Researcher (Advisor: Dr. Joanna Collingwood)	Coventry, UK Oct. 2016 - Jun. 2017
• International Institute for Product and Service Innovation, WMG B.Eng Student Researcher (Advisor: Mr. Graeme Knowles)	Coventry, UK Oct. 2016 - Jun. 2017
Conference Talks	
 MODUCON 2019 Evaluating customer-focused metrics for developing robust computer vision systems [LIN 	2019 [K]
• PyCon APAC 2019	2019
• Robot development with Python (Lightning talk) [LINK]	
 NVIDIA Jetson Meetup NVIDIA Jetson Nano for intelligent robot development 	2019
COMMUNITY	
• Software Bootcamp Instructor Grepp - "Programmers Autonomous Driving Dev course"	2022 - Present
• Community Leader Kakao community - "We will be SLAM Masters"	2019 – Present
• Tech Blog Computer vision and SLAM blog - "cv-learn blog"	2019 - Present
• Industry Seminar Samsung, HANCOM Academy, HANCOM InSpace, J.MARPLE	2019 – Present
• Charity Webinar Youtube webinar - "A tutorial on object pose estimation", "A tutorial on visual-SLAM"	2019 - 2020
• Study Group Lead MODU Labs Group Study - "Visual-SLAM", "Medical imaging"	2019 - 2020
• Book Translation Community book translation: "Introduction to Visual-SLAM"	2018 - 2019